Guide to the UE Organizers Records, 1937-2003 UE.7.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Organizer Records, 7-3-1.
  - Villarreal, Gabriel: Organizer Reports, 1970-1981 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Walborn, Judy, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Walborn, Paul, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Waldrep, James, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Waling, Hugh, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Walker, Brenda, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Walker, Frederick, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Walsh, Mary, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Walters, Charles, 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Wanko, William, 1947-1950 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Ward, Harold, 1953-1959 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Ward, Robert, 1945-1948 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Ward, William, 1946-1951 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Ware, David, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Washington, Bertram, 1950-1956 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Washington, Marion, 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Watkins, John, 1949-1953 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Waxler, Jonathan, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Weir, Irvin: Correspondence, 1947-1960 (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
  - Weir, Irvin: Organizer Reports, 1949-1960 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Wells, Rachel: Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Wells, Rachel: Organizer Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Wells, Roy Hudson Jr.: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Wells, Roy Hudson Jr.: Organizer Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Wendroff, Pepper, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Wheelck, Rex, 1946-1953 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Wheeler, Alonzo: Organizer Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Wheeler, Alonzo: Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Whitehead, Mary: Correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Whitehead, Mary: Organizer Reports, 1949-1955 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Williams, Mindy, 1999-2002 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Willis, James, 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Willis, Keith, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Wills, Paul, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Wilmore, Michael: Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Wilmore, Michael: Organizer Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Winters, Ethel, 1956-1958 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Wiseman, Eunice, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Woek, Ann, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Wojewocki, Leonard, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Womack, Melvin: Correspondence, 1961-1991 (Box 48, Folder 36-37)
  - Womack, Melvin: Organizer Reports, 1961-1989 (Box 49, Folder 01-02)
  - Wright, Charles, 1948-1955 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Yakish, Terry, 1993-1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Young, Robert, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Young, Ruth: Correspondence, 1944-1950 (Box 49, Folder 06-07)
  - Zack, Robert: Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Zack, Robert: Organizer Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Zeramby, Jacob, 1948-1958 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Organizer Applications, 7-3-2.
  Series Scope Content Note: This series contains applications completed by those who wanted to become union organizers for the UE. The applications contain information such as the prospective organizer's name, address, military service, prior union affiliation, and experience in electrical work. In addition to the completed forms, some files contain a photograph of the applicant and news clippings regarding their work prior to their involvement with the UE. Correspondence is also found within many of the files. These letters contain information regarding the applicant and their work with the UE, often concerning their wage and working status. Much of the correspondence was sent from UE national officers James Matles, Director of Organization, and Julius Emspak, General Secretary-Treasurer, to the applicant or District officials.
  - Abbate, Louis Joseph- Kushner, Sam (Box 50)
  - LaDassor, Gray R.- Zupan, Ray (Box 51)
  - Applications, 1940s (Box 52)